haha.nu 2015-03-24

# Privacy statement | haha.nu

**Privacy statement**

haha.nu will not sell your personal information, and you will not receive email from anyone but haha.nu if you register for an account or become a member. Registered users will be asked for certain personal information (name and email address), and certain information will be posted on a user page on the site.

**Collection of information**

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the user’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information such as the number of pages you view while at the website, downloads that have been made, and other general visiting patterns.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, and to notify users about updates on the website.

haha.nu also uses [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) to serve statistics information. For more information about Google’s Privacy Policy, please click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html).

**Third Party Advertising**

We use various third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Visitation information from our sites will be used to create user interest categories, delivering more relevant ads over time. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Changes of policy**

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that such practices are subject to change. We ask that our visitors periodically review this page to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy statement.
